Nicholas P. Santini

Phone: 502-500-2916

E-mail: nick.santini@uky.edu

Addr.: 2312 Remington Way Apt. 2305

Lexington, KY 40511

Objective

To be hired for an internship, co-op, or position at a company where I can further develop my engineering skills while earning a computer engineering degree from the University of Kentucky.

Profile

Skilled programmer with professional experience in Web Design and Development. Knowledgeable in many programming languages including Javascript, jQuery, PHP, Python, and C++. Possesses many skills in computer science and information technology, including certifications in both personal computers and networking. Currently working towards a bachelor's degree in computer engineering at the University of Kentucky.

Skills and Qualifications

- Web Design and Development
- Programming experience in Javascript, Python, C++
- CAD software experience
- 3D Printing experience
- Professional video editing experience

- TestOut Certified Network Professional
- TestOut Certified PC Professional
- Autodesk Inventor Certified
- Nvidia Fundamentals of Accelerated Computing with CUDA C/C++ Certificate

Professional Experience

Web Developer/Data Assistant

July 2012 - August 2018

- Hired for data entry position and worked up to web developer.
- Designed and implemented the company's ecommerce store.
- Created a website under contract with the Pentagon for the Pentagon Force Protection Agency.
- Engineered and developed a decontamination pool product.
- Led internal and remote IT support.



All Safe Industries

https://www.allsafeindustries.com

11360 Bluegrass Pkwy Louisville, KY 40299 502-499-7988

Organizations

Association for Computing Machinery

President

April 2019 – Present University of Kentucky

Engineering Student Council

Member

August 2018 – Present University of Kentucky

Team Wildcat (UK Athletics)

Leader

August 2018 – Present University of Kentucky

Education

University of Kentucky

Computer Engineering Major

August 2018 – Present Lexington, KY

Jefferson Community and Technical College

Associates of Science Degree

January 2016 – August 2018 Louisville, KY

University of Louisville

Pre-Engineering Major

August 2013 – December 2014 Louisville, KY